const questions = {
  "0": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The native token of Ethereum.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "ETH/Ether",
      "choices": ["ETH/Ether", "EHR", "ET", "THER"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Native token of Ownly.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "OWN",
      "choices": ["NLY", "OWN", "OWY", "OWLY"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Native token of SparkPoint.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "SRK",
      "choices": ["SRK", "SPT", "SPPT", "SKT"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Native token of MetaGaming Guild.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "MGG",
      "choices": ["MTG", "MEG", "MGG", "MGD"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Definition of DApps.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "Decentralized Apps",
      "choices": [
        "Developed Apps",
        "Digital Apps",
        "Decentralized Apps",
        "Dedicated Apps"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "New game to be launched by MGG.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "Meta Saga Warriors",
      "choices": [
        "Meta Game",
        "Saga Adventures",
        "Meta Warriors",
        "Meta Saga Warriors"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Meaning of NFT",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "Non Fungible Token",
      "choices": [
        "Non Forgettable Token",
        "Non Feasible Target",
        "Non Fungible Token",
        "No Food Today"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Most expensive crypto.",
      "score": 3,
      "answer": "Bitcoin/BTC",
      "choices": ["Ether/ETH", "Matic", "Bitcoin/BTC", "SRK"]
    }
  ],
  "1": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question":
        "The first open-source blockchain with smart contract functionality.",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Ethereum",
      "choices": ["Bitcoin", "Polygon", "DApp", "Ethereum"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Meaning of POS.",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Proof of Stake",
      "choices": [
        "Point of Sale",
        "Proof of Stake",
        "Percent of Statistics",
        "Person on Set"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Meaning of POW.",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Proof of Work",
      "choices": [
        "Proof of Work",
        "Person on Work",
        "Percentage of Work",
        "Piece of Wood"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Creator of Bitcoin",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Satoshi Nakamoto",
      "choices": ["Elon Musk", "Satoshi Nakamoto", "Michael Jordan", "Yao Ming"]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "A decentralized digital ledger.",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Blockchain",
      "choices": ["Hardware Wallet", "Ethereum", "Bitcoin", "Blockchain"]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Physical device that stores crypto assetsâ€™ digital keys",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Hardware Wallet",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Wallet",
        "Metamask Wallet",
        "Digital Wallet",
        "E-wallet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Data structure that is used for verifying a block",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Merkel Tree",
      "choices": [
        "File Tree",
        "Merkel Tree",
        "Block Verifier",
        "Secure Block Checker"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Which is not a type of blockchain",
      "score": 4,
      "answer": "Pi Chain",
      "choices": [
        "Public Blockchain",
        "Pi Chain",
        "Consortium or Federated Blockchain",
        "Hybrid Blockchain"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question":
        "Blocks in a blockchain are chained together by _____________.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Hash Value",
      "choices": [
        "Value of Transfer",
        "Hash Value",
        "Wallet address",
        "Block explorer"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question":
        "Used to build smart contracts and DApps on the Ethereum blockchain.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Solidity",
      "choices": ["C++", "C#", "Solidity", "Python"]
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question":
        "Total percent of nodes that hackers should control if they want to disrupt a blockchain network.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "51%",
      "choices": ["10%", "20%", "35%", "51%"]
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Meaning of DAO.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Decentralized Autonomous Organization",
      "choices": [
        "Decentralized Autonomous Organization",
        "Digital Award Offered",
        "Distributed Autonomous Organization",
        "Distributed Automatic Organization"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Meaning of DEX.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Decentralized Exchange",
      "choices": [
        "Decentralized Exchange",
        "Decentralized Extender",
        "Digital Exchange",
        "Developed Exchange"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question":
        "Process of depositing a cryptocurrency token or coin in a yield farming project or protocol.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Staking",
      "choices": ["Holding", "Buying", "Staking", "Burning"]
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question":
        "Type of cryptocurrency that always holds a stable price and is backed by fiat money.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Stable Coin",
      "choices": ["Bitcoin", "Alt Coin", "Stable Coin", "Ethereum"]
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question":
        "Version of the World Wide Web powered by blockchain technology.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Web3",
      "choices": ["Web1", "Web2", "Web3", "Blockchain"]
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "A virtual world that exists online.",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "Metaverse",
      "choices": ["Social Media", "Metaverse", "Blockchain", "Ethereum Network"]
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question":
        "Who shaped a cryptographically secured blockchain which started this technology on 1991?",
      "score": 5,
      "answer": "W. Scott Stornetta and Stuart Haber",
      "choices": [
        "W. Scott Stornetta and Stuart Haber",
        "Satoshi Nakamoto",
        "Elon Musk",
        "Bill Gates"
      ]
    }
  ]
}

export default questions
